Kniffin, Kevin Collection of University of Wisconsin System Collective Bargaining Files 6340
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kevin Kniffin Collection of University of Wisconsin System Collective Bargaining Files
1923-2011
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kniffin, Kevin
University of Wisconsin
Association of Wisconsin State University Faculties (AWSUF)
United Faculty and Academic Staff (UFAS)
The Association of University of Wisconsin Faculties (TAUWF)
The Association of University of Wisconsin Professionals (TAUWP)
6340
2.5 cubic feet
2.5 linear ft.
Records.
7735393
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 26, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 26, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6340 MB: Kevin Kniffin Collection of University of Wisconsin System Collective Bargaining TAUWP Buttons Memorabilia
Collective bargaining -- College employees; Kniffen, Kevin; American Federation of Teachers; Association of University of Wisconsin Faculties; Association of University of Wisconsin Professionals; Association of Wisconsin State University Faculties; United Faculty and Academic Staff; University of Wisconsin
7735393
- AWSUF Files. 1923-1971 (Box 1)
  - Letter to Ed Muzik Regarding AWSUF Historical Files, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AWSUF Constitution, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AWSUF Fulkerson Case, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AWSUF Governor's Budget for 1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - AWSUF Graduate Program Solution, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - AWSUF Improvement of Instruction Committee, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - AWSUF Legislative Committee, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - AWSUF President's Report, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - AWSUF Membership, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - AWSUF Retirement Academic Freedom and Tenure, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - AWSUF Salary Payment Plan, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - AWSUF Salary and Leave of Absence, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - AWSUF University Press, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - AWSUF Tenure Problem Wife - Husband, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - AWSUF Alternatives for Biennial Conference, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - AWSUF Biennial Conference April 1966 OshKosh (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - AWSUF Biennial Conference April 1964 Eau Claire (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - AWSUF Biennial Convocation and Tours April 1960 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - AWSUF Committee Conference March 1968 OshKosh (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - AWSUF Committee Conference March 1967 Eau Claire (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - AWSUF Committee Conference October 1966 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - AWSUF Committee Conference October 1965 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - AWSUF Committee Conference1965-66 1964-65 1963-64, 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - AWSUF Delegate Assembly April 1968 Whitewater (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - AWSUF Delegate Assembly November 1967 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - AWSUF Delegate Assembly April 1967 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - AWSUF Delegate Assembly November 1966 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - AWSUF Delegate Assembly November 1965 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - AWSUF Delegate Assembly April 1965 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - AWSUF Delegate Assembly April 1964 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - AWSUF Delegate Assembly October 1964 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - AWSUF Selection of President Committee 1965-66, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Board of Regents of State Universities, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Executive Committee (State), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - AWSUF Candidates for President Elect 1965 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Constitution Of ASWUF (State) (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - President's Reports (State), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - State President's Correspondence, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Delegate Assembly Nov. 5 1936- Oct. 21, 1965, 1936-1965 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - AWSUF Code of Ethics, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence File March 28, 1939 - Oct. 10 1947, 1939-1947 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - AWSCF Conf. Rooms 1964 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - AWSUF Convention 1966 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - St. Pt. AWSCF Conf. (1962) (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - AWSUF Meeting 62-64, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- TAUWF, TAUWP, USAF, University of Wisconsin System Files. 1973-2010 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Report on Affiliation by the Committee of Five (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Collective Bargaining (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - UW Bargaining Rights, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Nationwide Comparisons (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - United Council of UW Students, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Spoto, Ray, Compensation Recommendations 2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Senate Presentation the Murder Case (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - United Faculty and Academic Staff Local 223, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - TAUWF. Miscellaneous, 1980-1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - TAUWP. Local 3535 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - University of Wisconsin + General, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - TAUWP Miscellaneous, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - University of Wisconsin System Number of Ranked Faculty, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Wisconsin State Senates Bills, 1977-2006 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Wisconsin State Assembly Bills, 1973-1998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Biographies, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Political Endorsements, 2003-2006 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Messages for Legislators (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Court Cases, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Legislative Reference Bureau Drafter's Note, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - TAUWP Board of Directors Meeting Apr 6-9, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - TAUWP Board of Directors Meeting Apr. 25-26, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - TAUWP Board of Directors Meeting Aug. 8-9, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - TAUWP Board of Directors Meeting Dec. 5-6, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - TAUWP Board of Directors Meeting Sep. 23-24, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - TAUWP Board of Directors Meeting Dec. 9-10, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - TAUWP Board of Directors Meeting Feb. 24-25, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - TAUWP, Board of Directors Meeting Dec. 1-2, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - TAUWP Board of Directors Meeting Nov. 2-3, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - TAUWP, Delegate Academy Apr. 23-24, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - TAUWP Delegate Assembly Apr. 22-25, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - TAUWP. Delegate Assembly Apr. 21-22, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - TAUWP. Delegate Assembly Apr. 27-28, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - TAUWP. Delegate Assembly Apr. 18-19, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - TAUWP. Delegate Assembly Nov. 20-21, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Academic Staff Representative 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - UW System Faculty Representative Meeting Feb. 3, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - UW System Academic Staff Leadership Conference June 28-29, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - UW Academic Staff Leadership Conference July 23. 2009 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - TAUWF - Board of Regents Minutes 1973 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - UW Board of Regents 2004 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - AFT - Wisconsin Higher Education Council Mar. 24, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Academic Program and Tenure Committee, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - TAUWP/AFT Instructional Academic Staff Committee Oct 28, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Crisis in Higher Education Conference, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Higher Education Conference Apr. 3, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Madison Area Peace Coalition (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Competitive University Workforce Commission Meeting Mar. 12, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - UW System Academic Leadership Conference July 17-18, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Meeting Agendas/ Minutes, 1978-2007 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Press Releases, 2005-2008 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Clippings 1981-1993 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Clippings 2003-2008 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Publications. 1938-2011 (Box 3)
  - AFT - Wisconsin Constitution 2003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Constitution, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Notes: November
      Format: Publication
      Language: English.
  - AFT - Wisconsin The Professional 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: The Professional, 2007; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Notes: Vol. XXVI, No. 1 February
    - Item 2: The Professional, 2008; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Notes: Vol. XXVII, No. 1 January
    - Item 3: The Professional, 2008; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Notes: Vol. XXVII, No. 2 April
  - AFT - Wisconsin Professionally Speaking 2007, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Professionally Speaking, 2007; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - AFT - Wisconsin Cope. Capital Update 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Capitol Update, 2008; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Notes: April 14
    - Item 2: Capitol Update, 2008; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Notes: January 18
    - Item 3: Capitol Update, 2007; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Notes: December 14
  - AFT Wisconsin Local 3535. Labor Day Songbook 2006, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Labor Day Songbook, 2006; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Notes: September 4
  - Hawk, Timothy E. Employment Rights of UW-Madison Academic Staff 2000, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Employment Rights of UW-Madison Academic Staff, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Author: Timothy E. Hawks
      Notes: June 22
  - Kniffin, Kevin M. Organizing to Organize; The Case of the Long-Haul Campaign for Collective Bargaining Rights 2011, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Labor Studies Journal, 2011; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Fiscal Bureau Recruitment and Retention of High Demand 2009, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Recruitment and Retention of High Demand Faculty and Academic Staff, 2009; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Notes: May 19
  - Mintz, Bernard; The CUNY Experience 1971, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: The Cuny Experience, 1971; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Author: Mintz, Bernard
  - Moberly and Mulcany. Public Employment Labor Relations 1974, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Public Employment Labor Relations, 1974; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Author: Moberly, Robert B., Mulcahy, Charles C.
  - TAUWF. Advocate 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: Advocate, 1985; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Notes: July 3
    - Item 2: Advocate, 1985; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Notes: April 11
    - Item 3: Advocate, 1984; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Notes: November 1
  - TAUWF/WFT/AFT Perspectives 1976-1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Perspectives, 1981; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Notes: Summer
    - Item 2: Perspectives, 1978; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Item 3: Perspectives, 1977; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Notes: Spring
    - Item 4: Perspectives, 1976; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - TAUWP. Advocate 1989-2005 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Advocate, 2005; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Notes: March
    - Item 2: Advocate, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Notes: October 2
    - Item 3: Advocate, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Item 4: Advocate, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Notes: November 26
    - Item 5: Advocate, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Item 6: Advocate, 1995; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Notes: December 15
    - Item 7: Advocate, 1994; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Notes: May 13
    - Item 8: Advocate, 1990; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Notes: August 29
    - Item 9: Advocate, 1990; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Notes: May 18
    - Item 10: Advocate, 1990; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Notes: April 9
    - Item 11: Advocate, 1989; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Notes: December 1
    - Item 12: Advocate, 1989; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Item 13: Advocate, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - TAUWP. Comment 1996-2006 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: TAUWP Legislative Initiative, 2006; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: January 11
    - Item 2: Great News For Academic Freedom, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: August 1
    - Item 3: System Administration's Treatment of Academic Staf a Kinder and Gentler Employer, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: July 8
    - Item 4: 4.2% Raise for 2002-2003, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: May 17
    - Item 5: Dr. Sheri Klein vs. UW-System Board of Regents, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: April 25
    - Item 6: Tenure Alert, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: February 25
    - Item 7: Tenure Alert, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 8: Comment, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 9: Regents Adopt Dangerous Precedent, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: August 30
    - Item 10: Salary Alert: No Less Than 4.2%..., 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: September 26
    - Item 11: Evisceration of Tenure, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: September 10
    - Item 12: Comment, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: June 17
    - Item 13: Academic Freedom Endangered, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: November 5
    - Item 14: Comment, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: November 29
    - Item 15: Regents Harass Marder, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: May 21
    - Item 16: Comment, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 17: UW System Administration Deprives Us of Our Civil Rights We Can't Vote! What Are They Afraid Of?, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: May 7
    - Item 18: Comment, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: April
    - Item 19: Comment, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: March 16
    - Item 20: Comment, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: March 5
    - Item 21: Comment, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: February 28
    - Item 22: Comment, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: February 14
    - Item 23: Comment, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: January 30
    - Item 24: Comment, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 25: Comment, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: December 18
    - Item 26: Comment, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: December 12
    - Item 27: Comment, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: November 15
    - Item 28: Comment, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: October 12
    - Item 29: Comment, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: September 8
    - Item 30: Comment, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: July 14
    - Item 31: Comment, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: April 3
    - Item 32: Comment, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: March 24
    - Item 33: Comment, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: March 8
    - Item 34: Comment, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: February 23
    - Item 35: Comment, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: February 1
    - Item 36: Comment, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: January 24
    - Item 37: Comment, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: January 14
    - Item 38: Comment, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: December 13
    - Item 39: Comment, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 40: Comment, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: October 4
    - Item 41: Comment, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: September 17
    - Item 42: Comment, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: July 26
    - Item 43: Comment, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 44: Comment, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: June 23
    - Item 45: Comment, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: August 16
    - Item 46: Comment, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 47: Comment, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: May 10
    - Item 48: Comment, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: May 3
    - Item 49: Comment, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: April 26
    - Item 50: comment, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: March 11
    - Item 51: comment, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 52: Comment, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: March 4
    - Item 53: Comment, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: November 11
    - Item 54: Comment, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: November 2
    - Item 55: Comment, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 56: Comment, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: July 24
    - Item 57: Comment, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: April 27
    - Item 58: Comment, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 59: Comment, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 60: What TAUWP Has Done For You: A Brief Review, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 61: Comment, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: February 18
    - Item 62: Comment, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: September 2
    - Item 63: Comment, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Author: Muzik, Edward J.
      Notes: May 6
    - Item 64: Comment, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: March 17
    - Item 65: Comment, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: March 7
    - Item 66: Comment, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: March 3
    - Item 67: Comment, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: January 9
    - Item 68: Comment, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: January 17
    - Item 69: Comment, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: February 3
    - Item 70: Comment, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: January 28
    - Item 71: comment, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: November 20
    - Item 72: Comment, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 73: Comment, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: October 18
    - Item 74: Comment, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: April 29
    - Item 75: Comment, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: October 14
    - Item 76: Comment, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: September 28
    - Item 77: Comment, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: September 16
    - Item 78: Comment, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: September 6
    - Item 79: Comment, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: August 23
    - Item 80: Comment, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 81: Comment, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 82: Comment, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: March 29
    - Item 83: Comment, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: March 12
    - Item 84: Comment, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: March 1
  - TAUWP. News 2007-2009 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: TAUWP News, 2007; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Notes: Vol. 3, No. 5 Feb
  - University of Wisconsin - Madison. Madison Institute 1999-2004 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Madison Initiative, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - University of Wisconsin System Fact Book 1978-1999 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Fact Book, 1978; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - University of Wisconsin System. Mission 1999, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Mission, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - University of Wisconsin System. Teaching Academic Staff on the UW System 1998, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: Teaching Academic Staff in the UW System, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Notes: June 5
  - UFAS. Comment, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: Comment, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 2: Comment, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Notes: March April
    - Item 3: Newsletter, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Notes: December
    - Item 4: Comment, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Notes: August
    - Item 5: Comment, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Notes: May
    - Item 6: Newsletter, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 7: UW Budget Meeting, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Notes: September 13
    - Item 8: Comment, Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 9: Newsletter, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Notes: September
    - Item 10: Newsletter, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 11: Newsletter, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 12: Newsletter, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 13: Newsletter, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 14: Newsletter, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Notes: March-April
    - Item 15: Newsletter, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 16: Newsletter, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 17: Newsletter, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 18: Newsletter, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 19: Newsletter, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 20: Newsletter, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 21: Newsletter, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 22: UW Budget Meeting, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Notes: Wednesday, september 13
    - Item 23: Gender Equity Meeting A Success, Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 24: Newsletter, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 25: Newsletter, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 26: Newsletter, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - UFAS. Defender 2005-2007 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: Defender, 2007; Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
      Notes: February
    - Item 2: Defender, 2007; Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Item 3: Defender, 2007; Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Item 4: Defender, 2007; Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Item 5: Defender, 2007; Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Item 6: Defender, 2006; Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Item 7: Defender, 2006; Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Item 8: Defender, 2006; Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Item 9: Defender, 2006; Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Item 10: Defender, 2006; Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Item 11: Defender, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
      Notes: Vol 4 Issue 5
    - Item 12: Defender, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Item 13: Defender, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
      Notes: Vol 4 Issue 4
    - Item 14: Defender, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Item 15: Defender, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Item 16: Defender, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
      Notes: Vol 4 Issue 3
    - Item 17: Defender, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
      Notes: Vol 4 Issue 2
    - Item 18: Defender, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - UFAS. Flyers 2002-2007 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: Health Insurance Costs Demonstrate Need for Fairness and Rights, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 2: July Bulletin, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 3: State Assembly Decimates UW-Madison and UW-Extension, 2007; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
      Notes: July 11
    - Item 4: What's Wrong with UW-Madison's Employment of Lecturers?, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
      Notes: February 21
    - Item 5: UFAS Office Hours, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
      Notes: Wednesday, May 2
    - Item 6: Your $700 Missing Paycheck, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
      Notes: June 24
    - Item 7: Letter, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
      Notes: July 10